Szymon Skrzyński

Senior Developer w Voicefox

Summary

I'm PHP and Java programmer with 9 years of experience (5 years of career experience). I worked in many projects in many companies - from small, beginning startup to big, adult companies. I worked one year totally remotely in two companies - I'm orderly and I can communicate and clearly explain ideas, problems and solutions when someone is not next to me.

I'm fascinated with programming, what you can notice looking on my own projects below.

I'm interested in algorithms, big data and machine learning (especially in image recognition, but natural language processing and speech recognition is also interesting). To learn machine learning I wrote three ML algorithms and special environment - there're described below.

I like to write and read clear code, splitted into separately modules. I write code using my knowledge of design patterns and principles for secure web applications. I'm enthusiast of code reviews and test driven development.

I worked in the backed (PHP, Java, Zend Framework, Laravel), with databases (MySQL, PostgreSQL, MS SQL, MongoDB), with search engine (Elasticsearch) and in the frontend (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery).

Experience

Senior Developer at Voicefox maj 2017 - Present

PHP Developer at Brand24 kwiecień 2016 - Present

- Big data
- TDD
- Code reviews
- PHP 5
- PostgreSQL
- Elasticsearch
- RabbitMQ

PHP Developer at Skillveo

wrzesień 2015 - marzec 2016 (7 mies.)

- PHP 5
- Laravel 5.12 i Eloquent
- MySQL
- Elasticsearch

PHP Developer at LiveSpace.pl czerwiec 2014 - styczeń 2015 (8 mies.)

- Google Calendar integration
- PHP 5
- Zend Framework 1.12
- PostgreSQL
- JavaScript, jQuery

PHP Developer

czerwiec 2013 - maj 2014 (1 rok)

- PHP 5
- Zend Framework 1.12, Doctrine
- PostgreSQL
- JavaScript, jQuery

PHP Developer at Mediovski sp z o.o.

lipiec 2012 - październik 2012 (4 mies.)

- PHP 5
- Zend Framework 1.12
- PostgreSQL
- JavaScript, jQuery

PHP Developer

październik 2011 - kwiecień 2012 (7 mies.)

- PHP 5

Education

Uniwersytet Wrocławski Engineer's degree, IT, 2016 Zespół Szkół Ponadgimnazjalnych nr 1 w Siedlcach Technik, IT, 2007 - 2011

Szymon Skrzyński

Senior Developer w Voicefox



Contact Szymon on LinkedIn